These are [music] seven accessories that
make my iPhone into a productivity
machine. As someone who works on myself,
all the times I work in cafes, airports,
and trains. [music]
And so I've set up my iPhone to
basically replace my computer and even
my main camera when [music] I'm not at
home. Personally, I use the 17 Pro, but
even if you're not on the latest iPhone,
there's still a lot more they can do
with it than [music] you probably
thought was possible. So, I'm sure
you'll get something out of this video.
So, the first item is the magic stand.
There are a lot of MagSafe stands out
there and I've luckily tried most of
them. And this one by far is the best
one I've ever seen. What's unique about
this is that not only is it the thinnest
MagSafe stand [music] I've ever seen, it
also gives you the most optimal viewing
angle. This setup is super convenient if
you ever do FaceTime calls or even do
any sort of meetings because you can
just pop it up anytime
>> [music]
>> and
do a FaceTime call. Like, I use this all
the time, probably like multiple times
every single day. And even if you just
wanted to watch a video, like you're
eating, you want to watch a video, this
[music] is a really optimal setup. You
can You can adjust it in many different
angles. You could do landscape if you
wanted. And it [music] just collapses
and kind of disappears into your phone.
I think it's a lot more ergonomic than
[music] holding your phone down here or
using a traditional MagSafe stand, which
is at a low viewing angle. If you ever
need to record something, this is also
really convenient. Like, for example, I
[music] like to take videos of myself
playing guitar so I can capture my
progress. It's really convenient because
[music] I never have to find something
to prop up my phones. Because it's
completely made out of metal, it also
feels really [music] nice when it's
collapsed and doesn't have like a
plastic or fake leather as you might
[music] see on many MagSafe stands. It
comes in a bunch of different colors
that you can use to match to your phone,
but I think the black looks super sick
on the silver iPhone. But, the only
issue with this stand as a productivity
setup for your iPhone is that the only
thing you can really do is watch a video
or be in a meeting. And that's where
this next device comes in. So,
>> [music]
>> this is a folding keyboard made by the
company iClever. When you unfold it,
it's basically [music] a split keyboard.
And surprisingly, it's really nice to
type on. You can easily switch between
three Bluetooth devices. So, you can
also switch between your laptop, your
iPhone, or any other device pretty
easily. And with this setup, it's
actually pretty overpowered because all
you need to do is to bring this
keyboard, which literally fits in your
back pocket, and you can do work for
many hours at a cafe, like writing,
going through emails, and even vibe
coding. There are a bunch of keyboard
shortcuts already built into iOS and
they're pretty much exactly the same as
macOS, so it's really easy to learn. For
example, command space to open an app,
alt-tab [music] to switch between
different apps, and there's a lot more
for specific apps. I think using a
keyboard with my phone definitely
transformed the way that I see my phone.
There were tasks that I didn't think
were possible or realistic to be done on
my phone [music] that I can now do just
on my phone. For example, if you just
needed to do some writing at a cafe,
there's really no need to bring your
entire laptop or even iPad
>> [music]
>> to the cafe. You can just bring a small
folding keyboard like this. But with
this keyboard specifically, even when I
bring my MacBook to a cafe [music]
outside, now I like to also bring this
one because it makes it so that my
wrists are in a more ergonomic position
and I can have the screen popped up a
little bit higher. I think if you didn't
have [music] a dedicated keyboard at
home, you could definitely use this as
your dedicated keyboard. Like, the
battery life is surprisingly long
[music] and once you collapse it, it
immediately goes into sleep mode.
Originally, I got this to connect to my
projector, which runs on Android, like I
don't have a TV, and this makes it
easier to search stuff up, pause, play,
[music] and I still use it for my
projector because it's really easy to
switch between different devices. But
yeah, with this setup, with your phone
like this and your keyboard out like
this, there's something about the setup
where your phone and hands are in this
position that you're less likely going
to be doomscrolling or wasting time on
your phone. Like, this is just a
productive position. A lot of times I
like doing my flashcard reviews on my
phone with this position because it's a
little bit less distracting than my
computer, where I might have different
apps or windows open. But at this point
the setup with the screen and the
keyboard like this, I know what you're
thinking. And yes, you can actually
connect a mouse to iOS now. If you turn
on this setting in your [music] phone
called Assistive Touch, you can now
connect your mouse to your phone and
there's actually a cursor. [music] So,
for me personally, I like the MX Master
series. I previously had the MX Master 3
that I gave to my girlfriend, so I'm
using this MX [music] Master travel
size, which is just a little bit
smaller. This is actually my main mouse
that I use at home. And if I'm going out
to a cafe and I have my sling, a lot of
times I'll just bring the two of them
and put them in my sling and [music] I
basically have a setup that I can do
work for
as many hours as I need. But with this
[music] trio though, the stand, the
foldable keyboard, and the mouse, you
essentially have an iPad micro [music]
that you can use to actually get work
done. There's even ways that you can
remotely log into your computer from
your phone, which I'm going to show in
the next video where I talk about what's
actually on my phone. But probably the
worst thing that could happen if you
were out in a cafe with this setup
[music] is if your phone died. And so,
that's where this next item [music]
comes in and it's the Anker 165 watt
power brick, which can charge every
single one of these devices and your
phone multiple times. So, usually the
iPhone 17 Pro battery life is actually
really good and I don't think I've ever
had it die in a single day if I had it
fully charged in the morning. But if
you're doing extended writing or vibe
coding at full brightness on your phone,
it may drain after a couple hours. Some
of you guys recommended this to me in my
last video and I can say this is
probably one of the most overpowered
>> [music]
>> battery packs on the market. So, this is
surprisingly compact, but it's the
[music] maximum legal limit that you can
actually bring on an airplane. But the
thing that makes this battery pack stand
out is that there's a built-in USB-C
cable here that works as [music] a hook
and there's also another super long one
that is retractable. Since switching to
the iPhone 17 Pro, pretty much all my
devices are USB-C and with the keyboard,
mouse, and phone, they're all USB-C, so
you can charge two of them at once while
you're working if you need to. This
power brick is also fast enough that it
can charge my MacBook [music] at regular
speed. So, if you do any sort of
traveling, this is also convenient
because you don't have to look for an
outlet. This has 25,000 mAh,
>> [music]
>> so it can charge your phone multiple
times and your computer one time.
Recharging this brick is actually really
easy and super fast as well. So, all you
have to do is take this plug and plug it
into any USB-C [music] hole and then it
will charge this one. So, you don't have
to plug another wire into this. The
other day I went to Disneysea and this
came in handy because it could charge
both of our devices fully and it still
had more power left over. But the next
item helped me replace my DSLR when I'm
on the go. So, usually when I film
YouTube videos, I'm using my good
camera, which is the DSLR that you're
seeing right now.
But iPhone cameras have gone to the
point now where they're essentially more
than enough for making YouTube videos.
There's been more than a few times that
I filmed videos just with my iPhone and
the way that I can do that is with this
MagSafe accessory. This is a portable
MagSafe monitor that you can plug into
iPhone and see what's on the front. So,
that means you can fully utilize the
back camera, which is going to be way
better quality. Obviously, this is most
useful if you make content, [music]
but even if you don't make content, this
could be useful if you wanted to use the
back wide-angle camera for a call or if
you wanted to take group photos. But if
you do make content or you want to make
content, this thing could help you save
thousands of dollars. So, I got this
camera a few years ago. This is a
expensive DSLR and I've tested it with
the latest iPhones and it's actually
kind of scary how little difference
there is. So, maybe I'll just show you
an example. So, let me just attach this
right here. Okay, so I have my stand
right here and then I have the monitor
right here. And then I'm going to record
myself. Okay.
All right, so this is the DSLR and then
this is the iPhone. Let me know what you
think. Is there a big difference? I
don't think there's a big difference. I
think if I fully switch to the iPhone,
nobody would even notice. And a lot of
times the iPhone is actually easier
because there are no settings to mess
with and you can't really mess up the
recording because on an expensive
camera, you have a bunch of settings
that you have to learn how to use. Uh
the only issue with this if you're
recording on your iPhone is that the
storage can add up pretty quickly and
that's [music] where the next item comes
in. So, this is just a super small SSD
that you can plug into your phone or
computer.
So, it just plugs into the bottom of
your phone like this and you can either
use it while you're filming or you can
just use it to transfer files and
[music] you can just take this and plug
it into
any other devices. Like, you can plug it
into
your computer or your iPad or anything
else. If you take any 4K videos on
iPhone, this is going to be a massive
life improvement
because 4K videos always take super long
to AirDrop and sometimes they might
fail. And [music] so, this just makes it
an
actual wired connection and makes it way
faster. But even if you don't film
anything, [music] this is also a pretty
nice compact SSD. Like, this one I have
is 2 terabytes and I can use it to back
up a lot of different files. But the
next item really helped me tie
everything together and helped me
actually compartmentalize my phone as a
productivity machine. And brick.
So, this [music] is basically just a NFC
chip that you can tap with your phone
and then they have a pretty nice to use
app that once you tap it, it will just
block
a certain list of apps. So, this is
actually meant to help people reduce
their screen time, but that's actually
not the main reason I use [music] this.
I just use this to block out a certain
group of apps when I'm trying to do
work. So, basically, you can set up
different categories of apps you want to
block. And when those apps are blocked,
you won't get any notifications from it.
>> [music]
>> So, I have one list that is called
silence and basically, when I activate
it, I won't get [music] any
notifications from people messaging me.
Obviously, you can just use Do Not
Disturb, but I think this is a step
better because you actually don't see
the notifications at all, so there's no
temptation to pull you in. But uh pretty
much everything you can do with the
brick, you can also just do it in iPhone
automations [music]
for free, but I'm a big fan of this form
factor and I think what the company's
doing is really cool. Oh yeah, with the
brick, I think it's nice because you
have to make the conscious decision to
be like, "Okay, work time is over."
Uh whereas [music] when it's in Do Not
Disturb, you can easily just switch
between two different modes. But if you
do want to reduce your screen time, I
did make a video that's [music] like one
of the most viewed videos on this
channel about how I reduced my screen
time by 80% that you can check out. One
more bonus upgrade that I want to show
you guys and may- maybe only
>> [music]
>> a small percentage of you guys would
appreciate this is that I have this
sticker that completely eliminates the
camera wobble when you lay it down flat
[music] on the table. So, my iPhone,
when you lay it down on the table, it
has no wobble at all. But, yeah, I
basically got these rubber stopper
stickers for my apartment, and I had a
bunch of them left over, and I found out
that they were the exact height of the
camera bump. And so, I put them on the
flashlight, and then [music]
the camera wobble completely
disappeared. So, yeah, I think that was
a pretty nice upgrade. It's probably not
worth buying a pack of these stickers
just to remove the camera wobble, but if
you have something like this laying
around, it could be helpful to you.
[music]
But, yeah, that's it for this video. Let
me know what you thought of this,
and
make sure to follow [music] me on
Instagram. I'm trying to post more on
there.
And also, what what do you think of my
beard? I've been growing out since the
last video, and uh I'm not sure if I
want to keep it or or shave it.
Uh
yeah, also,
>> [music]
>> do you like this angle better? This is
behind my my desk. Do you like this
angle better, or do you like the
previous angle, where it's facing the
window?
Let me know in the comments. [music]
Uh I'm still trying to find out what is
the best place to film
>> [music]
>> in my apartment.
And uh yeah, so I'm going to make a
video about what's on my iPhone in the
next video, like show you my setup, and
also really useful apps [music] that
I've been using. And also, I posted a
video on my channel memberships, which
is an apartment tour, so if you're
interested in the apartment tour, you
can check it out. But, yeah, hope you
found this helpful, and I'll see you in
the next video.
Let's get it.
>> [music]